tep.com 2019-04-16

# Privacy Policy – Tucson Electric Power

Last Updated: June 22, 2016

#### Privacy Commitment

Tucson Electric Power Company ("TEP" or "we") recognize that you care how your personal information is used and shared. We are committed to protecting the privacy of our customers. This Privacy Policy describes the privacy practices governing www.tep.com (our "Website") and TEP's Mobile App (the "Mobile App"), including how TEP collects, protects, uses, discloses and disposes of Customer Information. For the purpose of this Privacy Policy, "Customer Information" means any personal information gathered by TEP about an identified individual through the use of our Website or Mobile App, including, but not limited to, name, e-mail address, postal address, telephone number, Social Security number, and bank account information. Customer Information does not include information that is publicly available or information collected by any third party that may link to or be accessible from our Website or Mobile App.

#### Scope of Policy

Please read this Privacy Policy carefully to understand TEP's policies and practices regarding Customer Information. If you do not agree with these policies and practices, you may choose not to use our Website or Mobile App. This Privacy Policy applies to all users of this Website and Mobile App ("Users"). By accessing the Website or using the Mobile App, you consent to this Privacy Policy and to the collection and use of information by TEP as specified herein. This Privacy Policy is subject to the TEP Terms of Use which take precedence over any conflicting terms contained herein. Except as otherwise provided in the Terms of Use, this Privacy Policy is the entire privacy policy for this Website and the Mobile App and supersedes any prior communication on this topic. This Privacy Policy may change from time to time (see Changes to Our Privacy Policy) and continued use of this Website or Mobile App after changes have been made is deemed to be acceptance of those changes. Please check our Privacy Policy periodically for updates. The Website or Mobile App may contain links to non-TEP websites which are outside our control. Clicking on those links may allow the third party operator of those websites to collect or share information about you. This Privacy Policy does not apply to information that you provide to or is collected by any third party website. Please check the privacy policies of any non-TEP website prior to providing personal information.

#### Collection of Customer Information

The primary reason TEP collects and maintains Customer Information is to provide services to our customers and offer additional services which may be of interest to customers like you. We do not collect personal Customer Information from you unless you voluntarily provide it to us. As explained below, information collected by TEP falls into two general categories: (1) Customer Information voluntarily supplied, and (2) information gathered as a result of automatic data collection technologies.

#### Voluntarily Provided Customer Information

You may choose to provide Customer Information directly to TEP by a number of means, including through the Website or Mobile App registration process, filling out various forms, responding to surveys or contacting us through the Website or Mobile App. Such Customer Information is stored in a secure database and may be retrieved and changed through "My Account." If you do not want to provide Customer Information to us, you may take advantage of the publicly available content on the Website or Mobile App without registration, however, the automatic data collection technologies may still collect the information described below.

#### Automatic Data Collection Technologies

As you navigate through and interact with our Website and Mobile App, we may use automatic data collection technologies to collect information about your equipment, browsing actions and patterns to operate the Website and Mobile App effectively and improve our services. The technologies we use for automatic data collection may include cookies (small data files stored on your computer by your web browser upon visiting a website or placed on your smartphone or device), web beacons (small files that provide TEP with Website and Mobile App statistics such as how many people have visited a particular web page) and similar technologies. When you access the Website or Mobile App, TEP's web servers automatically record certain data, including but not limited to your Internet service provider, IP address (which may identify your general geographic location or company), domain name, browser type, device type, device ID, operating system and the times and dates of your visits to our Website or use of the Mobile App. Cookies are important for the proper functioning of websites and mobile applications and enable TEP's systems to remember log-in details, provide secure log-in, collect statistics to optimize the functionality of the Website and Mobile App and provide services tailored to your interests. Although you may set your browser to block all cookies, including TEP's, we recommend that you leave cookies turned on to take full advantage of all of the Website's and Mobile App's features. We may also use automatic data collection technologies to gather information about your interactions with our Website and Mobile App in order to provide you with information related to services and products offered by TEP which may be of interest to you. The Website and the Mobile App do not collect Customer Information automatically, but we may tie information gathered automatically to the Customer Information you have given to us. If we combine automatically gathered information with your Customer Information, we will treat the combined information as Customer Information.

#### Use and Disclosure of Customer Information

It is TEP's general practice to treat Customer Information as confidential and use it in a limited number of ways. When you provide Customer Information when requesting services or information on the Website or through the Mobile App, TEP uses that information for the purpose for which it was provided. We may use your Customer Information to provide you with access to certain features on the Website and Mobile App and notify you when Mobile App updates are available. We may use Customer Information to inform you about products and services offered by or in connection with TEP, to educate customers about safety and energy efficiency, for billing and collection purposes, for identity verification purposes, to meet regulatory requirements, to monitor and enhance our relationship with you, to notify you about changes to our Website and Mobile App and to further TEP's business objectives. We may also use your Customer Information for any other purpose after obtaining your consent. TEP may disclose Customer Information to specific non-affiliated third parties who are providing services for your benefit on behalf of or jointly with TEP, such as, but not limited to payment processing services and services related to our energy efficiency programs. In such situations, TEP limits the amount and type of Customer Information provided to that which is necessary to provide the services. We include language in our contracts with third parties designed to protect the privacy of your Customer Information and limit its use to the purpose for which it was provided. TEP does not sell your Customer Information to third parties. Except as otherwise expressly stated in this Privacy Policy, TEP does not intentionally disclose Customer Information to non-TEP entities unless you specifically authorize such disclosure; we believe disclosure is required to comply with laws, regulations, legal processes or regulatory requests; or disclosure is necessary to protect the rights, property, health and safety of TEP, our customers, employees or others. We may disclose Customer Information to other companies and organizations as we determine may be necessary for fraud protection, to mitigate the risk of identity theft, to enforce and apply our own Terms of Use, if we believe we have evidence of a violation of computer security laws and for credit risk reduction. TEP reserves the right to transfer Customer Information in connection with the sale of all or part of TEP's capital stock or assets to the entity acquiring such stock or assets.

#### Retention and Destruction of Customer Information

Subject to limits imposed by applicable law, TEP retains Customer Information as long as your account is active and for such additional time as we believe such information is required or will be useful to fill a business or law enforcement need. TEP reserves the right to remove any such Customer Information from its records.

#### Security

The security of your Customer Information is important to us. We have implemented and continue to maintain reasonable administrative, electronic and procedural safeguards designed to protect Customer Information from accidental loss and from unauthorized access, use, alteration and disclosure. Although TEP believes these procedures are adequate, no method of storing or transmitting information over the Internet or via the Mobile App, including email communications, is completely secure. Accordingly, TEP cannot guarantee the security of your personal information transmitted to our Website and Mobile App and transmission of Customer Information is at your own risk. If you do not want TEP to know any particular Customer Information, do not include it in anything submitted to the Website or Mobile App.

The safety and security of your Customer Information also depends on you. In using certain services offered on our Website and Mobile App, you may be assigned a user ID and may choose a password. You are solely responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of your user ID and password, and are responsible for all activities that occur under your user ID and password. We suggest that you do not share your password with anyone. You agree to immediately notify TEP of any unauthorized use of your user ID, password or Customer Information, or any other breach of security regarding the Website and Mobile App of which you are aware. TEP will not be liable for any loss arising from your failure to comply with these security requirements and you agree to hold TEP harmless from any and all losses that arise from any such failure to comply. TEP is not responsible for any information, including Customer Information, which may be gathered at a linked or other third party website. Although TEP has taken precautions to ensure that linked websites follow a similar privacy policy, TEP cannot guarantee their policy or practices and urges you to review the individual policies of each website you visit. In no event will TEP be responsible for any third party website policies or actions.

#### Changes to and Acceptance of Our Privacy Policy

TEP is continuously working to improve its Privacy Policy to remain in compliance with evolving laws. TEP accordingly reserves the right, in its sole discretion, to modify the Privacy Policy from time to time. Any such change will be effective upon the posting of the revised Privacy Policy at the Website and Mobile App. If such changes are made, TEP will notify you by revising the "Last Updated" date on the top of the Privacy Policy. If we make material changes to how we treat your Customer Information, we may choose to notify you by e-mail to the address you provided. You are responsible for ensuring that we have a valid e-mail address for you. By continuing to use the Website and Mobile App after the posting of any such changes, you accept and agree to the Privacy Policy as modified. For your convenience, you may wish to print out this Privacy Policy for your records.

#### E-mail Marketing

TEP enables you to opt out of marketing communications by using the "unsubscribe" link included in such emails. However, non-marketing communications are not subject to a general opt-out and may contain important information regarding your account.

#### Compliance with Laws

TEP will comply with applicable federal and state laws regarding its collection and use of your Customer Information and will limit any disclosures accordingly.

#### Children's Privacy

We believe in the importance of protecting children's privacy online. Our Website and Mobile App are not intended for use by children under 13 years of age. TEP does not knowingly collect nor do we desire to collect personal information from children under the age of 13. If you believe that we may have received personal information from a child under 13 without verification of parental consent, please notify us so that we may immediately delete that information. For more information about the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act, visit the FTC's web site at [www.ftc.gov](https://www.ftc.gov/).

#### For California Residents

We do not share Customer Information with third parties for their direct marketing purposes.

#### Contact Us

If you have questions or comments regarding our Privacy Policy, please contact us by sending an email to [corpcomm@tep.com](mailto:corpcomm@tep.com) or writing a letter to:

Privacy Matters  
c/o TEP  
PO Box 711  
Tucson, AZ 85702-0711

You can also call us at 520-884-3630.
